<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaffys - Katie Tigue</title>
    <description>I&#39;m Katie Tigue, and I&#39;m a 4th year GDD Major. My hobbies include playing League of Legends and trying new beers.
</description>
    <link>katie@mail.rit.edu/</link>
    <atom:link href="katie@mail.rit.edu/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 15:03:54 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 15:03:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Flight</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first blog post on my new website. I will be using this page for two classes I am taking this semester, Humanitarian FOSS Development and Business &amp;amp; Legal Aspects of Free/Open Source Software. This is my first time taking a class like this, and I’m really excited to explore the world of Open Source Software. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start off my open source adventure, I wanted to try something new and create a website with open source software. I heard of Jekyll from a friend, so I wanted to try and set it up. I’ve never used a command line tool before and I’m have some experience using Github. I installed &lt;a href=&quot;http://iterm.sourceforge.net/&quot;&gt;iTerm&lt;/a&gt; to use at my command line client, and I installed &lt;a href=&quot;http://brew.sh/&quot;&gt;Homebew&lt;/a&gt; which made it really easy to install Ruby and all of the Ruby Gems I needed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;gem install jekyll&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boom. Look I’m a pro. It’s really easy for me to run a local instance of Jekyll, just by going to the directory that my project is in and typing a quick command. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-bash&quot; data-lang=&quot;bash&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, whenever I want to create a new blog post, I just create a new markdown file with the date and the title as the file name and drag and drop it into the _posts folder. I can write all of my posts in markdown, which would also makes my life pretty easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Github, I’m using my github.io page to host my webpage, so I just push my website to that repo and it automagically updates it for me. Bam. Beautiful, simple blog page. &lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 09:46:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>katie@mail.rit.edu/bizleg/2015/02/03/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">katie@mail.rit.edu/bizleg/2015/02/03/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bizleg</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
